# **Leandro Bordon**

Full Stack Developer

Rosario, Argentina (GMT-3) (+54) 9 3412284866 <u>leandrobordondev@gmail.com</u> https://linkedin.com/leandro-bordon

Full-stack Developer with +3 years of experience in developing high-impact applications. I have worked under scrum methodologies, MVC Architecture, DDD, design patterns and best practices. I'm a self-taught enthusiast and passionate about algorithms and functional programming. I'm focused on building consistent interfaces and solid infrastructures, constantly seeking new challenges to push myself out of the box.

# **EXPERIENCE**

## Match, FullStack Developer — Oct, 2022 - Nov, 2023

- Development with a team of engineer a <u>digital storytelling platform</u> based in Next.js and Wordpress
- I was assigned to develop the Pronto website from scratch with custom theming, and custom modules development.
- We were an international team of engineers working under Scrum methodologies.

Tech Stack: HTML, CSS3, JavaScript, React.js, Next.js, Zustand, Jest, React Testing Library, Prisma ORM, CSS, Sass, PHP, MySQL, MongoDB, TailwindCSS, Styles Components, WordPress, Custom Themes, WP Cli, Custom Plugin, Git, GitHub, Jira (SCRUM).

# Air Computers, Full-Stack Developer — Mar, 2020 - Agu, 2022

- I participated in the development of a FullStack app for the distribution of Microsoft digital licenses (ESD). I worked with the support of the Microsoft team throughout the process. We won an award for performing and sales time for the Microsoft Partner Program in 2021.
- I collaborated with a team of Engineers to develop a new ecommerce platform. We use continuous integration and we Improving 80% of performance.
- To fix and Create Wordpress Custom Plugins

Tech Stack: JavaScript, React.js, Zustand, Jest, React Testing Library, CSS, Sass, PHP, Laravel 9, MySQL, MongoDB, TailwindCSS, Styles Components, WordPress, WP Cli,, Custom Themes, Custom Plugin, Jquery, Git, GitHub, Jira (SCRUM).

#### CoderHouse, JavaScript Instructor — Feb. 2020 - Sep. 2020

- I have taught over 25 students both basic and advanced concepts of JavaScript programming.
- 90% satisfaction rate from my students on the platform.
- Conducted special classes focused on agile methodologies and object-oriented programming.

Tech Stack: Javascript ES6, HTML, CSS, Npm, Jquery, Node.js, Express, MySQL.

### **SKILLS**

**Programming Languages:** <u>Advanced:</u> <u>Javascript, PHP, Node.js; <u>Intermediate:</u> Typescript; <u>Basic:</u> Python. **Frameworks Tools:** <u>Advanced:</u> React.js, Express.js, Wordpress; <u>Intermediate</u> Next.js, Laravel; <u>Basic:</u> Nest.js.</u>

Data Base: Advanced: MongoDB, MYSQL; Intermediate: GraphQL;

**Agile:** Scrum with Jira

Languages: Intermediate: English B2+; Native: Spanish.

#### **EDUCATION**

Computer Systems Analysis - Ciudad Autónoma de Buenos Aires, Argentina. Computer Systems Analysis, Mar 2017

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

**Javascript Bootcamp** – coderhouse.com. 2019 **React.js Bootcamp** – coderhouse.com. 2019